# Adenuga Oluwatimilehin A.

Phone: +234 705 506 0823 Email: timi.nihel@gmail.com Address: Ikeja, Lagos, Nigeria. LinkedIn: <u>Adenuga Timilehin</u>
Github: <u>Thi-Mee</u>
Twitter: <u>@Timi\_Nihel</u>

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a Software engineer. I've gained fundamental knowledge of software design and development and worked on projects. I'd love to combine my skills in Software engineering with my passion for creating things and solving problems around.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**ALX AFRICA - Software Engineering Intern** 

MAY 2022 - PRESENT

- I employ best coding practices on my different software development projects
- Employed the skills gained here to build lots of projects
- Worked on a lot of tasks assigned almost everyday

Reskill Americans, US - Front End Development Tutor OCTOBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

- I make resources including videos and articles for students to read or watch.
- I help with any problem or issue they have and have regular virtual classes to check on them.

**Zuri Team Inc., Nigeria** - Full Stack Development Intern MAY 2022 - JULY 2022

- Learnt backend development with django
- Cooperated with my team of 15 to build a Metadata extraction web app
- Created and linked the Django Templates

#### **PROJECTS**

**Serverless Todo App** - A simple TODO application using AWS Lambda and Serverless framework

TechStack - AWS Lambda, Serverless, Auth0, TypeScript

## **Converted a Monolith App to Microservices**

TechStack: TypeScript, Docker, Travis Ci pipeline, Kubernetes

Simple Shell - A simple shell to replicate some of the functions of the Bourne shell (sh) on a unix operating system.

TechStack: C

Xtracto - A metadata extraction web application

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML5
CSS3, Bootstrap
JavaScript, React
Git and Github/BitBucket
Python, Django
Node.js and Express.js
C, C++
MySQL, MongoDB
AWS Services/Cloud development
CI/CD using Docker, Github
actions, Kubernetes

## **AWARDS/CERTIFICATES**

Web development Foundation Udacity

Cloud Development

**ALX Udacity** 

Responsive Web design Fundamental Udacity

Full Stack Web Development Zuri Team

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

## **EDUCATION**

Cloud Developer Nanodegree, Udacity

JULY 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

University of Lagos, Nigeria - BSc 2017 - 2023 B.Sc. ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING I did the frontend templating and routing TechStack: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Django